If you also want to invest in the share market and
want daily news, then
like the video and subscribe to the channel.  Here
we share
news of many companies together.  Be it IPO,
dividend news or news of a company
getting an order.  So you
must join the channel.  The number one news is from
HDB Financial Services.  It is going to
give a dividend of ₹2 to its shareholders.
Number two, SL Semiconductor has
given approval to sell its land here.
Number three is Elcan Engineering.
It has also given dividend.  An announcement of approximately ₹1.5 has been made.
After that comes Texmao
Engineering LED, it has got an order worth Rs 39
crore.  Next news here is about Saal B
Bhadra Finance LED.  It is raising around ₹15
crore here.  After that comes
ICICI LBRD.  It has also announced a dividend of ₹7.
After that, it has
got an order of approximately Rs 168 crore for SRM contract.  After that,
next is John Cocktail India.  It has also
secured an order here
from JSW Steel.  So this is also a big news
regarding this company.  And HDB Financial
Services Limited, their profit is
quite good this time.  Their quarterly
results are here.  So this is big
news for the shareholders of HDB Financial Services.
So for such updates, please
like the video and subscribe to the channel.
You will get such videos daily.
Thank you.